Contact

alizarinangel@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/megan-moon-76b766124 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals

CEN

Emergency Nursing

Megan Moon

BSN, RN, CEN

Fort Worth, Texas

Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry in leveled trauma centers, freestanding emergency centers, and speciality hospitals. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, has CEN, TNCC, ENPC, PALS, and ACLS.

Experience

Methodist Health System
Emergency Room Registered Nurse
October 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Dallas, Texas

trustaff

Emergency Room RN March 2016 - September 2016 (7 months)

Travel nursing

Plaza medical center ER RN June 2015 - February 2016 (9 months)

First Choice Emergency Room
Er rn
December 2013 - July 2015 (1 year 8 months)

Nightingale Nurses
Travel ER Nurse
November 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 2 months)

Texas Health Huguley Hospital Fort Worth South ER RN
May 2011 - October 2012 (1 year 6 months)

THR Harris Methodist azle ER RN July 2009 - January 2011 (1 year 7 months)

JPS Health Network ER RN August 2007 - July 2009 (2 years)

Scripps Mercy Hospital Trauma RN April 2007 - August 2007 (5 months)

West Jefferson Medical Center ER RN December 2006 - March 2007 (4 months)

JPS Health Network
Oncology RN
July 2006 - December 2006 (6 months)

Harris Methodist Fort Worth Nurse extern labor and delivery October 2002 - June 2006 (3 years 9 months)

Education

Midwestern State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing (2004 - 2006)